[upbeat rock music]
- Oof. - Sheesh.
- 哎哟。 - 天哪。
- Not good. - What's not good?
- 不太妙。 - 什么不太妙？
- The toppings. You loaded it with all the heavy ones.
- 配料。你全放了那些重的。
- You got pound cake. It's right in the name!
- 你拿了磅蛋糕。名字里都写着呢！
- Next time, Britt, go with the lighter,
- 下次，布里特，选些轻的，
more affordable toppings.
更实惠的配料。
Like sprinkles or nut dust.
比如糖珠或坚果粉。
- Got it.
- 明白了。
- Next.
- 下一个。
Oh, hey, guys. Welcome to Fro-Yo You Didn't.
哦，嘿，伙计们。欢迎来到‘你没试过的冻酸奶’。
Oh, fro-yo you did.
哦，你试过的冻酸奶。
We haven't had a pound caker in months.
我们已经好几个月没吃过一磅蛋糕了。
That'll be $32.
那将是32美元。
- Tried to warn you.
- 我试图警告你。
- I know it's chockers, but we don't have
- 我知道这很贵，但我们那里没有
all these fancy toppings where I'm from.
所有这些花哨的配料。
I'm just used to getting plain mangosteen.
我只是习惯于吃纯山竹。
- Whatever you just said, please say it again.
- 无论你刚才说的什么，请再说一遍。
- Mangosteen?
- 山竹？
- What's wrong with Natalie?
- Natalie怎么了？
- She's never twirled her hair like that before.
- 她以前从没那样转过头发。
- Or smiled.
- 或者那样笑。
- So, $32? - Forget it. It's on the house.
- 所以，32美元？ - 算了。算我请客。
I'm a sucker for accents.
我对口音没有抵抗力。
- Good on ya.
- 干得好。
- We're from Australia, too.
- 我们也是从澳大利亚来的。
- Yeah, what do we owe you, mate?
- 是啊，我们该付你多少钱，伙计？
- Mangosteen.
- 山竹。
- Not happening.
- 不可能。
- Yeah, yeah, nice accent, Dawn.
是啊，是啊，口音不错，Dawn。
- Can't blame her for trying.
不能怪她尝试。
- I'm in such a good mood, yours are on the house, too.
我心情很好，你的也算我请客了。
- Wow. - Thanks.
哇。
- Awesome.
谢谢。
- Looks like someone just got Britted.
太棒了。
- Yeah, she was totally flirting.
看起来有人刚被撩了。
- I'm flattered, but I've already got my eye
是啊，她完全是在调情。
on another girl.
我受宠若惊，但我已经有心仪的女孩了。
- So who is she?
那她是谁？
- Ooh, I bet that's who you're always drawing
哦，我打赌那就是你总是在素描本上画的那个人。
in your sketch book.
我还是不想说。
- I'd rather not say.
我不想搞砸了。
I don't wanna jinx it.
她还不知道呢。
She doesn't know yet.
哦！
[together] Ooh!
你知道我想‘哦’什么吗？
- You know what I wanna "ooh" about?
这个酸奶。真的很好吃。
This yogurt. It's really good.
嗯，是的。我可以习惯这个。
- Hm, yeah. I could get used to this.
我们以前从没免费得到过冻酸奶。
We've never gotten free fro-yo before.
你真棒。无论我们去哪儿，人们都想给你免费的东西。
- You're awesome. Everywhere we go,
- 你太棒了。无论我们去哪儿，
people just wanna give you free stuff.
人们总是想给你免费的东西。
- Oh, come on, guys. It doesn't happen that often.
- 哦，拜托，伙计们。没那么频繁。
- Here's some more toppings.
- 这里有些更多的配料。
The heavy ones. Shh.
重的东西。嘘。
- See, Britt? Things just fall in your lap.
- 看，布里特？事情总是落在你头上。
- Yeah, but never, ever in ours.
- 是啊，但从来不会落在我们头上。
[gasps] - Uh!
[惊呼] - 啊！
- Cold! Cold!
- 冷！冷！
- Yep, that had some pound cake in it.
- 是的，里面有一些磅蛋糕。
[laughter]
笑声
[upbeat music]
欢快的音乐
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐 ♪
[whistling]
口哨声
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐 ♪ ♪ 嘿! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一, 二 ♪ ♪ 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐, 呐 ♪ ♪ 一, 二, 三, 四! ♪
[cheerful music]
欢快的音乐
- It really is amazing to watch.
看着真的很神奇。
Britt just talks and people hand him free stuff.
布里特只要一开口，人们就会给他免费的东西。
- So I guess your phones are broken, huh?
- 所以我想你的手机是坏了吧，嗯？
- No, why? - 'Cause you didn't call me
- 没有，为什么？ - 因为你没打电话叫我
to come down here and get all this free stuff.
下来这里拿所有这些免费的东西。
- Don't worry. We'll go back later.
- 别担心。我们晚点回去。
- Can't wait to see what else he can get us for free.
- 迫不及待想看看他还能给我们弄到什么免费的东西。
- Oh, no, boys, you should be
- 哦，不，孩子们，你们应该
friends with Britt for who he is,
因为他是谁而和他做朋友，
not for what he can do for you.
而不是因为他能为你做什么。
- Listen to your mother, boys. It's not right
- 听你妈妈的话，孩子们。那样利用人是不对的。
to use people like that.
- 现在回去工作吧，Britt。 - 好的。
- Now back to work, Britt. - Yep.
- 现在回去工作，Britt。 - 是的。
- Sure thing. - [laughs]
- 当然可以。 - [笑]
- Sale on skates! Prices down under what you'd expect.
- 滑冰鞋大减价！价格低于你的预期。
Why walkabout when you can rollabout?
为什么步行当你可以滑行？
- Oh, look at 'em go.
- 哦，看他们滑得多好。
Ahh!
啊！
Do as we say, not as we do. - Right.
照我们说的做，不要照我们做的做。 - 对。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Okay, we've got corn dogs, soy candles and splat balls.
- 好的，我们有玉米热狗、大豆蜡烛和彩弹球。
Anything else you wanna add to the stuff we want
还有其他你想加到我们想要免费列表的东西吗？
Britt to get us for free list?
布里特，帮我们列个免费清单？
- Ooh, maybe tickets to something
- 哦，或许可以弄些活动的门票
- Poetry on Ice! - Foodie Fest!
- 冰上诗歌！ - 美食节！
- I'll go with you if you go with me.
- 如果你跟我一起去，我就跟你去。
- Hey, is that Dawn and Britt?
- 嘿，那是道恩和布里特吗？
- You don't have to change the subject.
- 你不必转移话题。
I get it, you don't wanna go.
我明白，你不想去。
- No, seriously. They're right over there.
- 不，说真的。他们就在那边。
And yes, who would wanna go to that?
而且，谁会想去那种地方？
- Is she getting free stuff without us?
- 她是不是在背着我们拿免费的东西？
- Hey! I want a--
A locket?
Yeah, I'm comfortable with that.
- That's weird. - Why would she hang out with Britt without telling us?
- I know what this is.
This is a house crush. - A what?
It's when two people under one roof
develop feelings for each other.
I see it all the time in my favorite reality show,
"12 People, One Toilet."
Do I need to explain more?
我需要解释更多吗？
- Uh, yes.
- 呃，是的。
- Most of the action happens while they're waiting
- 大部分的情节发生在他们排队
in line for the toilet.
等厕所的时候。
Tensions mount, sparks fly
紧张升级，火花四溅
and romance ensues.
然后爱情就发生了。
A house crush. - Oh.
房子里的暗恋。 - 哦。
A house crush, of course.
房子里的暗恋，当然。
- Now you get it! - No.
- 现在你明白了！ - 不。
That's reality TV This is real.
那是真人秀。这是真的。
They're clearly not in a house crush.
他们显然不是在暗恋房子。
I hope your right, because if they are,
我希望你是对的，因为如果他们是在暗恋，
and Mom and Dad find out, they're gonna
而且爸爸妈妈发现了，他们就会
send him back to Australia.
把他送回澳大利亚。
- So, you guys find a flavor you like yet?
- 所以，你们找到喜欢的口味了吗？
- Oh, we're still sampling.
- 哦，我们还在尝试。
- Is that so?
- 是吗？
- Thanks for helping me pick out the locket.
- 谢谢你帮我挑选这个项链。
I'm giving her this and the sketch I've been working on.
我要把这个和一直在画的素描送给她。
- [scoffs] So you're still not gonna tell me
- [嗤笑] 所以你还是不打算告诉我
who this mystery girl is, huh?
这个神秘女孩是谁，嗯？
- As soon as she knows, you'll know.
- 她一知道，你也会知道。
- Fair enough. Ooh! Let's hit the makeup counter.
- 公平。哦！我们去化妆品柜台吧。
- I thought you said you didn't have any more money
- 我以为你说你没钱了
- Psh, who needs money when I have
- 哼，有澳大利亚运通卡谁还需要钱？
my Australian Express card?
- 这是冻酸奶，不是免费酸奶。
- It's fro-yo, not free-yo.
[欢快音乐]
[upbeat music]
- 六支唇彩？七支眼线笔？
- Six lip glosses? Seven eyeliners?
一年的睫毛膏供应？
A year's supply of mascara?
- 是的，而且全免费。
- Yep and all for free.
- 是的，而且全都是免费的。
- And at what point did your phone break?
- 你的手机是什么时候坏的？
- It didn't. Why? - Because you didn't call me
- 没坏。怎么了？ - 因为你没打电话叫我下来拿这些免费的东西。
to come down and get all this free stuff.
呃，对不起，但布里特希望只有我们俩。
Uh, sorry, but Britt wanted it to be just us.
他让我帮他挑一条项链给一个特别的女孩。
He asked me to help him pick out a necklace
- 哦！她是谁？
for a special girl. - Ooh! Who is she?
- 我不知道。他现在还不想让任何人知道她是谁。
- I don't know. He doesn't want anyone
但他告诉我，当她知道的时候我也会知道。
to know who she is yet.
哦。好吧，我现在就知道了。
But he said I'll know when she knows.
你怎么知道的？
- Oh. Well, I know right now.
哦。好吧，我现在就知道了。
- How can you know?
你怎么知道的？
- Because it's obviously you!
因为显然是你！
You're the special girl.
你就是那个特别的女孩。
- What? Britt and me?
什么？布里特和我？
Come on, we live in the same house.
拜托，我们住在同一个房子里。
He's my foreign exchange brother.
他是我交换生兄弟。
- Have you seen "12 People, One Toilet"?
你看过《12个人，一个厕所》吗？
Tensions mount, sparks fly, romance ensues.
紧张升级，火花四溅，爱情随之而来。
- Yeah, well, nothing's ensuing here.
是啊，好吧，这里什么都没发生。
- Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- You know, I feel bad about earlier.
你知道吗，我对之前的事感到抱歉。
Tell me more about poetry on ice.
再多跟我说说冰上诗的事吧。
- Okay, so for the first three hours we--
好吧，所以前三个小时我们——
- And I'm out.
那我先走了。
- Hey, look. There's Britt. Maybe we can get to the bottom
嘿，看。那是布里特。也许我们可以弄清楚
of this whole house crush thing.
这个所谓的‘房子里的迷恋’是怎么回事。
- There is no house crush thing.
根本没有什么‘房子里的迷恋’。
- Then who's he smiling at with that dumb look on his face?
那他那副傻笑的样子是在对谁笑呢？
- If it were Dawn, why wouldn't he just
如果对象是Dawn，他为什么不直接
talk to her face-to-face? - Because then everyone
面对面地和她谈呢？因为那样的话，
would know he's in a house crush.
所有人都会知道他对某人有好感。
You really have to watch this show.
你真的得看看这个节目。
- You know, I wish we could talk face-to-face.
你知道吗，我希望我们能面对面交谈。
But with our situation, this is the way it has to be.
但在我们这种情况，只能这样了。
- I told you. Face-to-face.
我告诉过你，面对面。
Tensions mounting. Sparks flying!
紧张升级，火花四溅！
- Ow and shh!
哎哟，嘘！
- No, you're the cutest.
不，你才是最可爱的。
No, you are.
不，是你。
- Romance ensues. - Ow!
浪漫上演。哎哟！
- Mm-hmm. - Mae, you've been
嗯哼。
"mm-hmming" at me for 20 minutes now.
Mae，你已经对我‘嗯哼’了20分钟了。
He doesn't like me.
他不喜欢我。
- Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
Sorry, I've been eating peanut butter.
抱歉，我一直在吃花生酱。
And I was trying to tell you that my mouth was stuck.
我刚才想告诉你我的嘴被粘住了。
But about the whole Britt not liking you part,
但关于Britt不喜欢你的部分，
mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
- Mae, seriously, you've been watching
梅，说真的，你看的真人秀太多了。
way too much reality TV.
嗯，解决这个问题只有一个办法。
- Well, there's only one way to solve this.
你说过他总是画这个女孩的肖像，
You said he's always drawing portraits of this girl
所以我们可以看看他的素描本。
so we can look in his sketch book.
他不想让任何人看。
- He doesn't want anyone to look at it.
他很注重隐私。
He's very private.
如果他不想让人看，
- If he didn't want anyone to look at it,
他会把它留在这里，
would he have left it sitting out here
在咖啡桌上吗？
on the coffee table? - He didn't.
他没有。
You went up in his room, got it and put it there.
你上楼到他房间，拿了它并放在那里。
- Mm-hmm.
嗯哼。
- Hold on. We can't be sure Britt's talking to Dawn.
等等。我们不能确定布里特是在和道恩说话。
We need to get eyes on this.
我们需要亲眼看看这个。
- You're right. Let's move.
你说得对。我们走吧。
- Thanks for the lap. - And the fries.
谢谢你的膝盖。还有薯条。
- See? It's not Dawn.
看吧？这不是道恩。
- Ow. What do you mean? It's clearly her in a wig.
哎哟。你什么意思？这明显是她戴着假发。
- That hair color totally works on you.
那发色非常适合你。
- Hey! Stop hitting me. - No, you stop hitting me.
嘿！别打我。不，你别打我。
- No! - [struggling]
不！
- I wish you could be here with me in America, Debra.
我希望你能来美国和我在一起，Debra。
- I'm telling you, it's just like season four, episode 12.
我告诉你，这就像第四季第12集一样。
Sherril and Dave wore wigs so they could keep their secret.
Sherril和Dave戴了假发，以便保守他们的秘密。
- [sighs] I can't believe I'm saying this
我真不敢相信我这么说，
but I think you're right.
但我觉得你是对的。
It is Dawn - It is me.
是Dawn - 是我。
both: Told ya.
我们说过了吧。
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la la, la, la, la, la ♪
啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦
- This is bad.
这很糟糕。
If my parents find out that Britt has a crush on me,
如果我父母发现Britt对我有意思，
it's see ya, wouldn't wallaby ya.
那就拜拜了，不会再有下次了。
- No Britt, no more free stuff.
- 没有Britt，就没有免费的东西了。
- No more lip gloss, nail polish, mascara.
- 没有唇彩，指甲油，睫毛膏了。
- Soy candles, splat balls, all gone!
- 大豆蜡烛，彩弹球，全都没了！
- But it's not all about the stuff.
- 但不仅仅是关于这些东西。
You'd be losing a friend, right?
你会失去一个朋友，对吧？
- Uh--yeah, I mean, didn't you hear me?
- 呃——是的，我是说，你没听我说吗？
I said friend gloss, nail palish
我说的是朋友间的光泽，指甲的淡化
and I mascare about Britt.
我对Britt很在意。
- We need to figure out a way to crush this house crush
我们需要想办法解决这个对房子的迷恋
before it crushes us. - Yeah, but we just
在它把我们压垮之前。
need to talk to him. - Maybe I need to talk to him.
是的，但我们只需要和他谈谈。
both: Bad idea.
也许我需要和他谈谈。
- On "T-POT"-- "12 People, One Toilet"--
坏主意。
Dave was crushing hard on Sherril.
在《T-POT》——《12个人，一个马桶》——
But when Sherril went to tell him it was bad for the house,
Dave对Sherril非常迷恋。
it only made Dave crush harder.
但当Sherril去告诉他这对房子不好时，
- And eventually, Sherril couldn't resist Dave's charms.
这反而让Dave更加迷恋。
Once the housemates got wind of it,
最终，Sherril无法抗拒Dave的魅力。
they tried to talk to Sherril and Dave.
他们试图和Sherril还有Dave谈谈。
- But the minute they knew their crush was forbidden,
但一旦他们知道这段恋情是被禁止的，
it only pushed them closer together.
这反而让他们更加亲近。
- Well, no one's pushing us together
好吧，没人会把我们推到一起，
because I'm gonna push him away.
因为我打算把他推开。
- Okay, if we can't talk to him about his house crush,
好吧，如果我们不能和他谈他的房子恋情，
what do we do? - Research.
我们该怎么办？ - 做研究。
There's gotta be a book on house crushes.
一定有关于房子恋情的书。
- To the book store!
去书店！
- How is it that the book store has no books on house crushes?
书店怎么可能没有关于房子恋情的书呢？
- And how is their café out of cake pops?
- 他们的咖啡店怎么连蛋糕球都没有了？
- [scoffs] Sharing a small. Sad.
- [嗤之以鼻] 分享一小份。真可怜。
- Just ring us up.
- 给我们结账吧。
- Nice nut dust.
- 坚果粉不错。
That'll be $4.37.
总共4.37美元。
- We've only got four.
- 我们只有四个。
- Well, then, you've got 37 cents
- 那么，你有37美分的不是我的问题。
worth of not my problem.
继续。
Keep going.
- 现在多少钱？
- How much is it now?
- 4.39美元。 - 怎么可能涨了？
- $4.39. - How could it have gone up?
- Spittle.
- 口水。
Here, let me take care of it for you.
来，让我帮你处理。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Wha-- - There. Now it's $4.
什-- - 好了。现在4美元。
Bink.
宾克。
You know, if you'd brought your cute Australian friend,
你知道，如果你带了你那位可爱的澳大利亚朋友来，
this all could've been on the house.
这一切都可以免单。
- Well, then, we should get used to paying
- 那么，我们得习惯付账了，
'cause Britt's as good as gone.
因为布里特差不多要走了。
- What? Why? How? When? Where?
- 什么？为什么？怎么？何时？哪里？
- Soon. He's in the middle of a serious house crush with Dawn.
- 很快。他正和Dawn陷入一场严重的房子迷恋中。
When our parents find out, he'll be sent home.
一旦我们的父母发现，他就会被送回家。
- Oh, that's nothing.
- 哦，那没什么。
It'll be over before your parents find out anyway.
反正他们还没发现就已经结束了。
- How do you know?
- 你怎么知道？
- [sighs] I see a lot working here.
- [叹气] 我在这里工作，见得多了。
And trust me, at this age,
相信我，在这个年纪，
relationships are like fro-yo.
关系就像冻酸奶。
Neither is as satisfying as ice cream.
都不如冰淇淋来得满足。
Point is, you've got nothing to worry about,
关键是，你没什么好担心的，
as long as they don't advance to the old,
只要他们还没进化到老夫老妻那一步。
boring couple stage.
穿着运动裤，逛商场，
Wearing sweat pants, mall walking,
谈论自己身体发出的各种奇怪声音。
and talking about the weird noises their bodies are making.
基本上，就是那种已经放弃生活的人。
Basically, people who have given up.
就像他们。
Like them.
- 汤姆，那是你膝盖在响吗？
- Is that your knee making that noise, Tom?
- 我希望那是你的，安妮。
- I was hoping it was yours, Anne.
- 太可怕了。
- That was horrifying.
一旦情侣到了那个阶段，他们的爱太强烈了，无法拆散他们。
- Once a couple gets to that stage,
一旦情侣到了那个阶段，
their love is too strong and there's no breaking them up.
他们的爱太强烈了，无法拆散他们。
- This is great. Dawn and Britt
这太好了。道恩和布里特
are nowhere near the giving up stage.
还远远没到放弃的阶段。
- How do I look? - Like you've given up.
我看起来怎么样？
- Perfect. Gimme my mouth guard
像已经放弃了似的。
and fire up the big guns.
完美。给我我的牙套
- I'm surprised Dicky didn't take his fart machine
然后启动大招。
with him to Australia.
我很惊讶迪基没有带他的放屁机去澳大利亚。
- Oh, he packed his good one.
哦，他带了他的好机器。
This one doesn't go to wet.
这个不会弄湿。
Time to gross this guy out.
是时候让这家伙恶心一下了。
- Oh, hi, Nicky.
哦，嗨，Nicky。
- No, it's me...Dawn.
不，是我...Dawn。
- Oh, sorry. Nicky has the same bedtime routine.
哦，对不起。Nicky也有同样的睡前习惯。
- So, what do you think of your special someone now?
那么，你现在对你的特别的人有什么看法？
- [sighs] She's the best.
她是最棒的。
A real beauty.
真正的美丽。
- Well, you know what else I like to do before bed?
嗯，你知道我睡前还喜欢做什么吗？
Just let my body release all the impurities from the day.
就让我的身体释放一天的所有杂质。
[fart machine malfunctions]
[放屁机器故障]
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
[laughs] See, I'm lettin' myself go!
[笑] 看，我正在放松自己！
Yeah, just let it all out.
是的，把一切都释放出来。
Here we go, right now. [laughs]
现在就开始。[笑]
[farting sound] Ooh, ah, jeez.
[放屁声] 哦，啊，天哪。
Oh, ooh. [farts]
哦，哦。[放屁]
Sorry, that one just slipped out.
抱歉，那个不小心出来了。
[farts] Oof! [laughs, farts]
[放屁] 哎哟！[笑，放屁]
Stressful day. Oh. [farts]
压力山大的一天。哦。[放屁]
Sorry, that one is just a big one. [farts]
对不起，那个真是大个的。
Ooh, it's, uh, spicy. [farts]
哦，这有点，呃，辣。
[sighs] [farting]
（叹气）
- You are going to sleep very well.
你会睡得很好。
- Yeah. [laughs] [farts]
是啊。
Sounds like something's broken in there.
听起来里面有什么东西坏了。
Wish I could just shut it off. [farting]
真希望能把它关掉。
You know what I mean? Just press a button
你知道我的意思吧？就像按个按钮
and turn it off. [farting]
然后把它关掉。
[farting continues] - [mouthing]
- Oh.
哦。
Ooh. [farting]
Yeah. [laughs]
是啊。
Yeah. [farts]
[barks] [farting sounds]
汪汪
- That's his panic bark.
那是他惊慌的叫声。
- What's wrong, Squish?
怎么了，Squish？
[farting]
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
[farts]
[放屁]
Oh, no. We're too late.
哦，不。我们来得太晚了。
Sweat pants, body noises,
穿着运动裤，身体发出噪音，
They've advanced to the giving up stage.
他们已经进入了放弃阶段。
This is bad! - Yeah, tell me about it.
这很糟糕！ - 是啊，跟我说说吧。
She used up my good blemish salve.
她用完了我的好瑕疵膏。
- We have to take drastic measures.
- 我们必须采取极端措施。
We need to get in there
我们需要进去
and confront Britt and Dawn right now.
现在就面对布里特和唐。
[farting]
[放屁]
- Maybe we should wait a bit.
也许我们应该等一会儿。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
[sniffing]
[嗅]
[barks] That's the signal.
[吠叫] 那是信号。
The coast is clear.
海岸是清的。
Nice job, Squish.
干得好，Squish。
- Where are Dawn and Britt?
Dawn和Britt在哪里？
- Yeah. [laptop chiming]
是啊。[笔记本电脑发出叮声]
Looks like Dawn's right here,
看起来Dawn就在这里，
calling Britt's video chat.
正在呼叫Britt的视频聊天。
- Well, should we answer it?
- 嗯，我们应该接吗？
- Of course we should answer it.
- 当然应该接。
We need to tell her to stop this now.
我们需要告诉她现在就停止这个。
Well, look who we have here.
嗯，看看我们这里是谁。
- G'day, I'm looking for--
- 你好，我在找——
- Oh, we know who you're looking for.
- 哦，我们知道你在找谁。
And you need to stop looking for him
而且你需要停止找他
because this thing is over.
因为这件事已经结束了。
- Yeah, Dawn, this house crush has gotten out of control.
- 是的，Dawn，这种对房子的迷恋已经失控了。
- What--my name's not Dawn.
- 什么——我的名字不是Dawn。
It's Debra. And I have no idea
我的名字叫黛布拉。
what a house crush is. - It's when two people
而且我完全不知道什么是‘房子恋情’。
who live under the same roof fall in love.
就是指住在同一个屋檐下的两个人相爱了。
- Fall in love?
相爱？
- Yeah, and it was fun while it lasted, huh, chicky?
是啊，虽然挺有趣的，不是吗，小妞？
- But now it's over, baby.
但现在结束了，宝贝。
Time for you to quit Britt.
是你放弃布里特的时候了。
- Yeah, and your Australian accent is terrible,
顺便说一句，你的澳大利亚口音真糟糕，黛-布拉。
by the way, Dee-bra.
谁是黛-布拉？
- Who's Dee-bra? - You are--wait a minute.
你是--等等。
♪ ♪
- ♪ La, la, la, la, la, la la, la, la, la, la ♪
- ♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪ ♪ 啦，啦，啦，啦，啦 ♪
- So Britt's special someone
- 所以布里特的特别的人
is a girl who lives in Australia named Debra
是一个住在澳大利亚名叫黛布拉的女孩
who looks exactly like me.
她长得和我一模一样。
- Those are the facts. Yes.
- 这些都是事实。是的。
- And you thought it was me and broke up with her.
- 而你以为那个人是我，所以和她分手了。
- Also the facts. Yes.
- 这也是事实。是的。
- But we only broke up with her because we thought
- 但我们和她分手是因为我们以为
you and Britt were a couple.
你和布里特是一对。
- Why would you think that?
为什么你会这么想？
- Well, the sweat pants, the blemish salve,
嗯，运动裤，瑕疵膏，
the farting-- it all points to couple.
还有放屁——这一切都指向情侣关系。
- I was only doing that because I was trying
我那样做只是因为我试图
to avoid being a couple.
避免成为情侣。
- Hm. Well, then, there's no house crush.
嗯。那么，就没有暗恋了。
This is good news. - There is no good news.
这是好消息。
We just broke up with Britt's girlfriend
没有好消息。
before he got a chance to ask her
我们刚刚在Britt有机会问她之前
to be his girlfriend.
和他女朋友分手了。
- Britt's gonna hate us.
- 布里特会恨我们的。
He's not gonna get sent back to Australia.
他不会被送回澳大利亚。
He'll go there on his own.
他会自己去的。
- [sighs] You need to call Debra back
- [叹气] 你需要给黛布拉回电话
and tell her it was all a mistake.
告诉她这一切都是误会。
- Great idea. We should do that.
- 好主意。我们应该这么做。
We can't do that. She blocked him.
我们不能这么做。她把他拉黑了。
Now what do we do? - Oh, I'm so glad
现在我们该怎么办？ - 哦，我很高兴
you're all down here. - Britt!
你们都在楼下。 - 布里特！
- Hello! - Everything's fine.
- 你好！ - 一切都好。
- I know I've been a bit secretive the last few days
- 我知道我最近几天有点神秘兮兮的，
and I'm sorry.
我很抱歉。
- It's okay. - We're not perfect either.
- 没关系。 - 我们也不是完美的。
- You know, I've been nervous about the girl I like.
- 你知道，我一直在为我喜欢的女孩感到紧张。
But I think it's time I tell you about her.
但我想现在是时候告诉你们关于她的事情了。
Her name is Debra.
她的名字是黛布拉。
- Really? - Debra?
- 真的吗？ - 黛布拉？
- That's a total surprise.
- 这真是完全出乎意料。
- She lives in Australia. - Really?
- 她住在澳大利亚。 - 真的吗？
- Australia? - Also a surprise.
- 澳大利亚？ - 也是个惊喜。
- By now she would've gotten to look at
到现在，她应该已经看到我寄给她的画像了。
the portrait I sent her.
所以明天，当我们视频聊天时，
So tomorrow, when we video chat,
我打算正式向她表白，让她成为我的女朋友！
I'm going to officially ask her to be my girl!
真的吗？明天？
- Really? - Tomorrow?
惊喜连连啊。
- And the surprises just keep on coming.
我知道！我都等不及明天快点来了。
- I know! I can't wait for tomorrow to get here.
我觉得他好像没那么兴奋。
- I don't think he seemed that excited.
他明明是兴高采烈地跳起来的。
- He was exuberantly bounding. - I saw it differently.
我看到的是另一番景象。
- Okay, unless we can get in touch with Debra
好吧，除非我们能联系上黛布拉
and straighten things out, we're gonna have to
把事情理顺，我们得
fake that video chat. - Well, how do we do that?
假装进行那次视频聊天。 - 那我们该怎么做呢？
- Simple, we make a fake Australia
- 简单，我们在后院造一个假的澳大利亚，
in our back yard, get a fake locket,
弄一个假吊坠，
a fake portrait and a fake Debra.
一幅假肖像和一个假Debra。
- Uh, where are we gonna get a fake Debra?
- 呃，我们去哪儿弄一个假Debra？
- Someone call for a fake Debra?
- 有人要假Debra吗？
- What part of Australia is Debra from?
- Debra来自澳大利亚的哪个地方？
New Jersey?
新泽西？
All right, so I've set up Britt's computer
好了，我已经设置好了Britt的电脑
so when he gets the call, it'll look like
所以当他的电话来时，看起来就像
it's coming from you.
是从你那里打来的。
- Perfect. Everything's in place.
- 完美。一切都准备好了。
- Almost everything.
- 几乎所有事情。
Miles, get in here.
迈尔斯，进来。
- Why aren't you hopping?
- 你为什么不跳？
- I agreed to wear the costume.
- 我同意穿这套服装。
I agreed to let you put sandwiches in my pouch.
我同意让你在我的口袋里放三明治。
I even agreed to wear these boxing gloves.
我甚至同意戴这些拳击手套。
But I will not hop.
但我不会跳。
- You drew the line in a really weird place, Miles.
- 你在这里划界限真是奇怪，迈尔斯。
- Now can we have our sandwiches?
- 现在我们可以吃三明治了吗？
- All right, fine.
- 好吧，好吧。
Who had the Reuben?
谁拿了鲁本三明治？
- That's me.
- 是我。
[upbeat rock music]
- It's go time.
- 是时候开始了。
[laptop chiming] - [gasps] Yes!
[笔记本电脑发出提示音] - [惊讶] 是的！
My Debra. Debra, uh, hi.
我的黛布拉。黛布拉，呃，嗨。
- [chuckles] G'day, mate!
- [轻笑] 你好，伙计！
- How's your day going so far?
到目前为止，你的一天怎么样？
- So far, so g'day.
到目前为止，还不错。
- Did you get my package?
你收到我的包裹了吗？
- Ooh. I did.
哦，收到了。
They're gorgeous.
它们很漂亮。
- I'm glad you like them
我很高兴你喜欢它们
because I've been meaning to ask you
因为我一直想问你
Debra, would you--
德布拉，你能...
Is that a kangaroo?
那是袋鼠吗？
Carrying deli mustard?
背着熟食芥末？
- [laughs] Well, it is a kangaroo crossing.
[笑] 嗯，这是袋鼠过马路。
Am I right, mate? [laughs]
我说得对吧，老兄？[笑]
So, uh, do you wanna ask me something?
所以，你想问我点什么吗？
- Yes, I did.
是的，我想问。
I--I think there's something wrong
我……我觉得那只袋鼠有点问题。
with that kangaroo.
呃，没有哦。他这样很正常。
- Uh, nope. That's normal for him.
他只是因为现在我不和他拳击而感到沮丧。
He's just been depressed 'cause I won't
这让我也感到难过。
box him right now.
那你去和他拳击吧，让他高兴起来。
- Well, that makes me sad.
好，没问题。[笑]
Go box him. Cheer him up.
去和他打拳击，让他开心点。
- Okay. [laughs]
- 好的。[笑]
I guess I'll just go box him, then. [laughs]
我想我就去和他打拳击吧。[笑]
[sighs]
[叹气]
- Don't do this, Dawn.
- 别这样，Dawn。
- Come on, we have to make this look real.
- 来吧，我们得让这看起来真实。
So just go down.
所以你就倒下吧。
- I'm not going down.
- 我不会倒下的。
You go down.
你倒下。
- No, you go down.
- 不，你倒下。
不，你下去。
- Uh! Ooh!
啊！哦！
[grunts] - Ohh!
（咕哝声）哦！
- Will you excuse me for one second?
你能让我离开一会儿吗？
[punching continues]
（继续打斗声）
Psst, psst, Dawn!
嘘，嘘，Dawn！
Don't punch him in the pouch.
别打他的口袋。
I've still got my egg salad sandwich in there.
我还在那里放了我的鸡蛋沙拉三明治。
What'd I miss?
我错过了什么？
- It was amazing.
太精彩了。
First punch, right to the pouch.
第一拳，正中口袋。
- Will you excuse me one more second?
你能再等我一秒钟吗？
- That's my Debra.
那是我的Debra。
[knocking at door]
[敲门声]
It's open.
门开着。
- Britt?
Britt？
- Wait.
等等。
It's also my Debra.
那也是我的Debra。
What's going on? - That's what I came here
发生什么事了？
to ask you.
我正是来问你的。
And why are you watching a boy
你为什么要看一个男孩
eating egg salad out of a kangaroo's pouch?
从袋鼠的育儿袋里吃鸡蛋沙拉？
♪ ♪
- It was an honest mistake.
- 那是个诚实的错误。
There was a portrait and the mystery girl.
有一幅画像和那个神秘女孩。
- And, come on, it's--
- 而且，拜托，那是——
it's the same face.
同一张脸。
- Sorry, mate. I don't see it.
- 抱歉，伙计，我没看出来。
- Even I see it.
- 连我都看出来了。
- You know what I don't see?
- 你知道我没看到什么吗？
Someone unzipping me.
有人在解开我的拉链。
Come on, guys. I'm dying in here.
拜托，伙计们，我快闷死了。
I mean, I-- I'd do it myself, but--
我是说，我——我自己可以做，但是——
- But you look so cute and-- unzipping.
但是你看起来那么可爱，而且——在解开拉链。
- Anyway, we're sorry.
无论如何，我们很抱歉。
We only acted selfishly because we don't
我们只是自私地行动，因为我们不想
want you to get sent back to Australia.
让你被送回澳大利亚。
We love having you here.
我们很高兴你在这里。
- Yeah, and not just for the free stuff.
是的，不仅仅是为了免费的东西。
But also because we enjoy having you
也因为我们都喜欢有你作为我们家庭的一部分。
as a part of our family.
作为我们家庭的一部分。
- Apology accepted.
接受你的道歉。
I like you guys, too.
我也喜欢你们。
Even though you know nothing about Australia.
尽管你们对澳大利亚一无所知。
- What? I thought we did a pretty good job.
什么？我以为我们做得挺好的。
- A boxing kangaroo walking around with deli mustard
一个带着熟食芥末和纽泽西口音的拳击袋鼠？
and a New Jersey accent?
我买它的唯一原因是
The only reason I bought it was because
我以为那是Debra试图
I thought it was Debra trying to
让我忍不住笑出来。
make me break a laugh.
我无法相信你飞了这么远过来。
- I can't believe you flew all the way over here.
- 我真不敢相信你飞了这么远过来。
- I already bought a ticket. I had the feeling
- 我已经买了票。我有种感觉
he was gonna ask me to be his girl.
他可能会让我做他的女朋友。
So I wanted to surprise him.
所以我想要给他一个惊喜。
- I'm glad you did.
- 我很高兴你这么做了。
- So I'm gonna start that-- - No, but that wasn't the--
- 所以我打算开始那个-- - 不，但那不是--
- Do you see a kangaroo and two Dawns?
- 你看到一只袋鼠和两个Dawn吗？
- Yep. - And smell egg salad?
- 是的。 - 还闻到鸡蛋沙拉的味道吗？
- Yep.
- 是的。
- Wanna go back to the mall?
- 想回商场去吗？
- Yep.
是的。
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪